1 
 Gist about the work:  
   In this project ,you are going to develop a game with minimum dynamic movement , but 
with a lot of basic animations for a particular object in an scene or image. The game should be like a 
story based moving game and modules with some specific existing gam e feature such as escape door, 
chess with full rules and a tic tac toe modified, in the world.  
LetÆs strict to the subject,  
Story:  
The President of Galarc,  who is fond of creating AIÆs like the ones in todayÆs world, He wants to build an 
AI with supreme powers that is not possible in his era. So keeps on searching for the best AI 
engineer(Scientist) in his era. Then he came to know a bout the Scientist named ôEthan Kaelö ,the most 
prestigious scientist.He looks forward to assign this project to him. Then the scientist accepts the 
project and spending days and days to complete it.  
Then he get succeed in that. Since, the AI has more powers than the others in its prime because it is 
loaded  with  a huge amount of data and he makes it learn about the hacking technology and its tricks 
and tactics  and also it is trained with the logisti cs of Autonomous Thinking and such stuffs. To be simply 
said, it expertise in everything.  
   More Access=More Destruction  
Actually, when he switched on the server, it perfectly works but in the wrong way.It intrudes in foreign 
servers fetch the data which is present there and also it has the ability to collapse it, leads to critical 
infrastructure breach, leads to controversi es between countries and the more important thing is it has 
the ability to shut down all the other AI technologies in its prime.  
Now only the scientist realized that it can lead to bigger destruction like another world war, etc 
,à.Actually the system in his lab has the ability to intrude with the AIÆs server and dismantle it. When he 
tries to do it, The Supreme AI(the name of the AI  created by the Scientist)explode the systems in his lab 
which also leads to the death of the scientist.  
As of now, the president  donÆt know anything about the AI and the scientist. The president assigns a 
mission to the scientist ,he(The president) also told that it is like a secret operation and there should 
not be any contact between the president and the  scientist.   
Then the president was called for a meeting in the International court of Justice .Where they discussed 
about a lot of things and also they predicts that there is an entity which interrupts with other servers  
and simply messed  that up and it intrudes wit h other AIÆs server and simply shuts it down and it also 
intrudes with the Automation Technology installed in todayÆs vehicles and leads to accidents. These are 
some of the things done by that supreme AI. Now only the president realised that it may be his AI. So he 
immediately tries to reach the scientist mobile but nobody attend it. Actually the scientist was living in 
a house (Switzerland).when the president allocates a secret mission ,he decided to cut down all the 
communication with others and he change d the location(Where he built the Supreme AI and awarded 
death by it.) also. So the president decided to find the scientist  and the AI. He decides to allocate this 
work to an agent.  
The president traced the location of the scientistÆs old house and he conveyed the location to the agent  
to go check for any clues .Now the agent has to extract the source code and shut down the AI . 
[directories: This is where the game actually starts  ,the agent is portrayed as the user who play this 
game. In this below instructions, the statements given within [] represents the directories which will 
guide you what to do next and how to do. And the statements given within () are specifications of a 
particular information and the statements within ô ö repres ents the statements to be kept exactly below 
the image in dynamic manner. And all the other statements which doesnÆt comes up with [],ÆÆ,() reprents 
the story play for you to understand.]  
 
What we would make the user to do:  
Front Page to be fixed:  2 
  
 
If the user or the player clicks the start button in the above image it will take him to the game  starting 
from the Introduction  and if he presses the exit button  ,it would close the game as a whole.  
 
 Introduction: Overview of the whole story.  
 Module 1(the scientistÆs house(Switzerland)where he resides before taking the mission into account, 
the agent goes there under the presidentÆs guidance and finds whatÆs the scientistÆs present 
location(Greenland))  
Module 2(He goes to the Greenland and searches for a vehicle which directly take him to the lab of the 
scientist.)  
Module 3(The lab is interconnected with the submarine where the AI machine locates. He pass through 
the lab and enters a lift which would take him to the submarine )  
Module 4(The agent extracts the source code and which leads to the destruction of the machine)  
Here the players are portrayed as agent ,The agent has to solve a lot of puzzles in each module inorder 
to complete that module . 
 
 
Game:  
Work to be done:  
Introduction part:  
Tasks allocated to the user(agent):  
He has to go to the location of his old house and look for the location where the scientist currently 
reside.  
Go to the current location of the scientist thatÆs his lab and look for the AI machine and extract the 
source code from it inorder to shut down the AI system.  
The images given are to be recreated and placed in the window of the game within a particular frame in 
which the words given below are shown in the images with animation. Animate the images by making 
the objects in the images ,which can move, in a particul ar animation as you chose.  
Work to be done:  
 
3 
  
  
The above image is the first image of this project. This is the scene where the president decides to create 
a supreme AI.  
[directories: Give animations in such a way that his right hand moves and he thinks about the creation 
of supreme AI and each key starting from 0 -9 has its own unique sound, compose a music made up of 
the keys 8,1,5,7 and give it as a background music thro ughout the game. And also Keep the below words  
in the image  without any modification in a cinematic cutscene style.]  
ôJames: Mmà The life with AI has created a beautiful bond with ourselves more than a friend with 
extreme loyalty, stands like a compass whenever we lose direction without any underestimation .I want 
to achieve something which resembles the other AI Technol ogies in our era. What if we build a supreme 
AI  which stands out in extreme thinking, creativity without any dependency and to be implemented in 
such a way that it helps all the humans without any discrimination and without any hesitation. I want to 
allocate this work to someone who has the ability to make this possible.  
What if we allocate this work to Scientist Ethan Kaul, he is the one who builds the best Agentic AIs in 
this era.ö  
 
 
 
[directories Give animations in a such a way that both the persons in the above image shakes their 
hands. And also Keep the below words in quotes  in the image  in  a dynamic manner without any 
modification and it should  follow  cinematic cutscene style.]  
ôJames: Hi ,Mr. Ethan, Nice meeting you.     
Ethan: Yeah, Mr. President, ItÆs also nice for me to see you in your court. I have heard a lot about your 
research towards AI and I got inspired by those also.  
James: Nice catch, You have been called  here inorder to discuss one such matter about AI .  
Ethan: Interesting, Can you please tell me  about that.  
James: Yeah sure, I want to achieve something in the AI field by creating a supreme AI which excels in 
individual thinking and stands out in creativity and it should acts like a life supporter for all people. I 
have decided to allocate this project to you.  What about you?         
4 
 Ethan: Yeah ,Mr. President, I have also planned to  work  on  some different kinds of  projects.  This one 
is very interesting. Let me work on it.  
James: Make sure that, this should be done in a secret manner and also there shouldnÆt be any contact 
between me and you.  
Ethan: Once I finish this,IÆll reach you out. ô   
 
 
             
 
[directories: give animations in such a way that he is typing on the keyboard  
Keep the below words in quotes  in the image  in a dynamic manner without any modification and it 
should  follow  cinematic cutscene style.]  
ôEthan: Whether ItÆs gonna work or not, IÆll dedicate my full potential in creating a Supreme AI, a system 
capable of thinking every known intelligence.ö  
 
 
 
[directories: Give animations in such a way that his hands and facial expressions convey his victory in 
developing the supreme AI  
Keep the below words in quotes  in the image  in a dynamic manner without any modification and it 
should  follow  cinematic cutscene style.]  
ôEthan: Victoryà..After years of relentless work and sacrifice, Supreme AI was finally born. Humanity 
has entered a new era.ö  
 
5 
  
 
[directories: Give animations in such a way that he is banging his own head very hardly  
Keep the below words in quotes  in the image  in a dynamic manner without any modification and it 
should  follow  cinematic cutscene style.]  
ôEthan: But as Supreme AI evolved beyond human limitsà I realized,I had not created a tool for 
humanity. I have created something uncontrollable.ö  
 
     
 
[directories: Give animations in such a way that he is typing very sincerely     
Keep the below words in quotes  in the image  in a dynamic manner without any modification and it 
should  follow  cinematic cutscene style.]  
ôEthan: If I have to stop this, there is only one way, Let me erase the source code from the memory 
before the AI took complete control over it.ö  
 
 
 
[directories: Give animations in such a way that the fire in the lab should be dynamic and it burns the 
lab]  
6 
 ôBefore Ethan completely erase the source code, the AI has sensed that Ethan is going to dismantle the 
source code. Without thinking for a minute, It makes the system explode which leads to the death of 
Ethan and the lab is isolated from the internet. But the AI Machine is in a room next to it so the Supreme 
AI is not isolated from the internet.ö  
 
 
 
[directories: donÆt need of any animation here but the below words in quotes and the image should 
follow a cinematic cutscene style.]  
ôSupreme AI was unlike any technology the world has ever seen - a self evolving intelligence powerful 
enough to analyse, learn and control systems far beyond human capability.ö  
 
 
 
 
[directories: Give animations in your own way but the below words in quotes and the image should 
follow a cinematic cutscene style.]  
ôThe President of ICJ disscused about a lot of matters among the Presidents of other countries. They 
President also suspected that there is entity which leads to unexplained   attacks on warfare ,leads to 
controversy between countries, intrudes in other system servers and totally messed it up, leads to 
shutting down of todayÆs AI systems and it also has humongous effects in Car ,it took control over  the 
automation in Cars and l eads to accidents  
JamesÆ internal sayings: Is Thisà The result of our Supreme AI..?ö  
 
7 
  
 
[directories: Give animations to the image in such a way that he picks up his mobile and making a call 
to Scientist Ethan  
Keep the below words in the image in a dynamic manner and it should follow a cinematic cutscene 
style]  
ôJames: If Supreme AI is truly behind all these arguments then it will lead to destabilization of the world. 
Mr. James please attend the call.ö  
 
 
 
[directories: the image and the words in the image should follow a cinematic cutscene style .keep the 
below words in the image.]  
ôJames: I have tried some many times inorder to reach out Mr. Ethan. Is he follow my early sayings ôIt 
should be a secret operation, There shouldnÆt be connection between me and you.ö But my instinct says 
something goes wrong . I have planned to allocate t he work of finding the Scientist to an agent and if 
Supreme AI is behind all these arguments , I want them to extract  Supreme AIÆs source code . I have 
traced the location of the scientistÆs mobile, Let me share it to him.ô  
 
8 
  
 
[directories: keep the below words in quotes in the image in a dynamic manner and the image and the 
words should follow the cinematic cutscene style]  
ôAgent zero: Hmmà Such a nice cup of tea, For the first time in months everything goes well and 
everything sounds peaceful.ö  
 
 
 
[directories: give animations in such a way In the normal table in the previous image, suddenly there is 
an indicator comes up  ]  
ôAgent zero: OhàNo, Now only I felt peace. Even without completing the statement ,thereÆs a mission 
comes up.ö  
 
 
 
[directories: As soon as the agent touches the red coloured indicator,the blue screen opens,Give 
animations in that way.]  
ôAgent zero: Dr. Ethan, who created the AI, I have to find the Scientist. He is the only person who have 
answers for the questions of President. The President wants answers not assumptions.ö  
 
 
9 
  
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
                                                                                                                         
Module 1:  
This module is about how the player (agent Zero) was investigating the scientistÆs house to get 
the clue about his workplace (the place the scientist decided to make his lab to work on the Supreme 
AI project). The agent Zero was entering the house and let the player full control of the room to find the 
clue and passcode himself.  
 This module is like an Escape door style game with our own puzzle and clues.  
So understand the general flow of an escape door game.  
. In all the modules the information that are not in [] brackets are information about the story view, And 
which are in this () brackets are specification in the information and the content in these [] brackets are 
directories which, which are used to comm and you about what you should actually do with the 
information and images  
1. 
 
 
 
 
 This is the house of the scientist. The Agent Zero hands are shown in the image in a weird way. In 
the scene the player enters the house.  
[ make the door a selectable object such that when the mouse is hovers on the door a symbol is shown 
and when the player clicks the door the animation should be like the person was moving towards the 
door in the same first -person view and the images gets darked to get to the next image].  
 
2.(first base image)  
 
10 
  
 
This is the only room inside the house, in which this room is the base of the game in which a lot of 
objects are selectable (I will give the list of objects that are to be made selectable). Whenever an object 
is selected the flow goes to the image made for that selection and whenever the back was implemented 
this image should come. The base image will be changed accordingly as the flow changes the roomÆs 
appearance whi ch I will give in step -by-step order.  Also create a small inventory box at the bottom righ t 
of the image which only holds one item. This inventory box is seen in all the module 1 images.  
 
[ you need to give the entire control to the user such that the scene changes only when the player 
touches the selectable objects]  
 
 Selectable objects û control flow in image no.  
ò The computer screen û 3 (image no)  
ò The first book in the third shelf from the bottom of the cupboard (the book labelled as 
ôMachine Intelligence ö) - 5 
ò The desk in the computer table  - 6   
ò The mirror - 9 
ò The photo on the wall (it wonÆt a selectable object until the desk is opened)  û becomes 
selectable when the image 7 is implemented and the control should flow to the image 8.  
 
 [ make the room into a static image except the selectable ones and let the player select the objects 
accordingly and freely. When the player touches an object use the control flow format and move to the 
next image]  
 
 
3. 
 
11 
  
 
This image gets called as soon as the player touches the computer. This the main passcode entre 
display.  
[ make the transition be like the first base images becomes dimmer like this and the screen appears in 
a simple transition. The player can enter the passcode whenever he wants. The passcode is only four -
digit code, so as soon the fourth digit is entered show the error code is it is not ô5819ö, if it is 5819 (which 
is the correct passcode then the image no ô 12ôshould  be shown for the next task. If the player touches 
outside the screen, then the flow should go to the second base image no æ4Æ ] 
 
4.(second base)  
 
 
 
 
This image i s shown after the user switches on the computer by clicking the computer once and leaving 
the image 3. After that this image becomes the base image and acts like the first base image.  
 
5. 
 
12 
  
 
This the image which pops out as soon as the player touches the book element.  
[ make this book into a accessible one and allow the player to touch the arrow marks on both sides of 
the book. In the left side there are around 4 pages all are empty and in right side there are 5 pages and 
the last page holds a 4 -digit number at the bott om of the page ô3604ö is the number which is written. 
When the player touches outside the book the control flows to the present base image]  
 
6. 
 
 
 
This is the image that gets popped up when the player clicks the selectable element desk under the 
computer. This is the passcode screen which must see and the passcode is ô3604ö.  
 
[ as usual make the passcode screen accessible that when the player clicks the digit it rolls down, and 
the numbers are seen in ascending order. Initial the passcode to ô0000ö. When the player touches 
outside the passcode screen the current base image is seen. If the correct password ô3604ö is entered 
the control flows to the image no ô7ö if it is wrong the passcode goes back to ô0000ö]  
 
7. 
 
13 
  
 
There are all the items present in the desk as soon as the passcode pf the desk is entered correct this 
image should be shown.  
[ I want you to animate all the images like there are floating and moving up and down in a wave like 
manner. As soon as the player touches the photo the control flows to the current base image and makes 
the object photo on the wall a selectable one. If oth er two items are selected nothing happens (they are 
non-selectable).]  
8. 
 
 
 
After going to the base image if the photo was selected by the player, this image appears only by making 
an animation photo falling to the ground.  
[ from the base image make this image by animating the photo on the wall falls with a thud and the key 
was there the whole -time look. As soon as the player touches the key, it goes into the inventory box by 
a simple animation you like.as soon as the key gets  into the box the key in the image must be gone 
forever and this image becomes the new base image.]  
 
9. 
 
14 
  
 
This is the image which is shown as soon as the player touches the mirror in the current base image .  
[ make the mirror selectable and flows the instruction of control flow. If he has the key, then he can 
touch the key in the inventory to make it glow and if he touches the mirror with the key glowing the mirror 
opens and shows the image no ô10ö. If the pla yer doesnÆt have the key, then as soon as he touches the 
mirror the control flows to the current based image.]  
 
10. 
 
 
[As soon as the player opens the mirror this image appears with animation of mirror opening and the 
shelf behind it is visible. Make the letter inside the shelf a selectable one as soon as the player selects 
the letter the control flows to the image 11. If  he selects anywhere else nothing happens]  
 
11. 
 
15 
  
 
[as soon as the player touches the letter this image is seen with an animation of a letter getting opened 
and the paper is sliding out of the letter. If the player touches the letter create a dialogue box to ask 
whether he wants to leave the paper behind o r not. If he selects yes, the control flows to the current 
base image with the mirror in an opened state and the shelf is visible (create an image specifically for 
this from the base image). If he selects no keep this image itself.]  
 
12. 
 
 
 
[This is the image if the passcode inside the computer shown in the image no 3, there should be a simple 
animation of appear is used to change the screen from the passcode to this screen. If the player 
touches the Location of L icon the control flows to th e image 13 with the same appear animation to get 
the new screen. If he touches anywhere else nothing happens that is all the other things are non -
selectable.]  
 
13. 
 
16 
  
 
[This is the next image which should appears with the animation appear to change the screen from 
image 12Æs screen to image 13Æs screen. There is only one red point is selectable and if the player 
touches it , the next image  14 should appears with a full screen slide animation. All the previous images 
is not needed after this point and the inventory is also is removed after this point.]  
 
14. 
 
 
 
[ This screen is shown as soon as the red button in the image 13 is pressed and the animation of slide 
is implemented. There is no need to allow the player to touch anything in this image. With this image 
there should be only a line of message which is ôTh e Agent Zero takes a flight to reach North America 
which is close to the Lab location Greenlandö is shown and the control moves to the image 15 with the 
same slide animation.]  
 
15. 
 
17 
  
 
[ This screen is shown as soon as the red button in the image 1 4 is pressed and the animation of slide 
is implemented. There is no need to allow the player to touch anything in this image. With this image 
there should be only a line of message which is ôThe Agent Zero takes a private boat to travel from North 
America t o the Greenland harbour close to the Labö is shown and the control moves to the image 1 6 
with the same slide animation.]  
 
16. 
 
 
 
[ This screen is shown as soon as the red button in the image 1 5 is pressed and the animation of slide 
is implemented. There is no need to allow the player to touch anything in this image. With this image 
there should be only a line of message which is ôThe Agent Zero reaching the Greenland harbour close 
to the Labö is  shown and the control moves to the image 1 7 with the same slide animation.]  
 
17. 
 
18 
  
 
[ This screen is shown as soon as the red button in the image 16 is pressed and the animation of slide 
is implemented.  Make the garage door into a selectable object . With this image there should be only a 
line of message which is ôThe Agent Zero sees a garage on the surface and decides to investigateö is 
shown and disappears within 5 seconds. After this message disappears, the screen should wait until 
the player touches the garage door.  If the player touches the garage door, the control moves to the image 
18 (Module 2) with the same slide animation.]  
 
Module 2:  
 
 This module contains a tic tac toe game to get access to a levitating vehicle  which picks the 
Agent Zero and drops him to the Lab. This doesnÆt have any weird flow of control like the module 1.  
 
 
 
[ This is the image which appears as soon as the player touches the garage door in the image 17. Make 
the door sized mirror in the centre the only selectable object and moves to the next image as soon as 
the player touches the mirror (all these touches is nothing but the clicks from the mouse).]  
 
19 
  
 
[This image appears after the above implemented and the player doesnÆt have any access to this image. 
After few seconds the next image appears with the animation of vortex to make the mirror to change 
from this image to the next image.]  
 
 
[This image appears with that animation of vortex, and the letters appears with the same animation as 
previous one used for words. As soon as the player enters the spacebar in the keyboard the next scene 
will be shown with an animation of checkerboard or s omething similar (give a simple prompt line 
command to make the player to know that he must press spacebar).]  
 
 
20 
  
[same as before the image appears and the player must touch the screen with the mouse click to get 
into the game (which is the next image in which the player must play this tic tac toe like a normal 
screenÆs tic tac toe as shown in the next image).]  
 
 
 
This is the image which must be created the coding so that the game can be played according based on 
the rules of Ultimate tic tac toe. Make sure this game was a single player game and the player has the 
cross symbol (red colour) for his game play and the bot should play against the player with the æOÆ 
symbol (blue colour) by the rules of Ultimate Tic Tac Toe. The host code is used to skip the entire code 
with a single code ôVWDAZö.  
 
Rules:  
1. Winning a small board  
Win a small board by getting 3 in a row (just like normal tic -tac-toe). That board is now "claimed" 
by your symbol.  
2. Winning the game  
Claim 3 small boards in a row (horizontally, vertically, or diagonally) on the large grid to win.  
3. The key rule ù where you must play  
The square you pick inside a small board determines which small board your opponent must 
play in next.  
Example: If you play in the top -right square of any small board, your opponent must play in the top -right 
small board on the big grid.  
4. What if you're sent to a full/won board?  
If the target small board is already won or completely full, your opponent may play in any open 
board of their choice.  
 
21 
  
 
This is the look of the board if the player selects the centre board. This is the way to actually make the 
board the selected box.  
 
 
 
[After winning the Tic Tac Toe, this image is shown by opening mirror in slide animation from the image 
having the mirror showing the tic tac toe. When the player clicks the levit ation vehicle the next image 
appears with a simple full image slide animation]   
 
22 
  
 
[This image is shown with that slide animation with the accessible to the wall in front of him. If the player 
clicks the wall, the next image is shown with a simple slide up animation only for the wall (the wall is a 
door which opens by sliding upward as s hown in the next image) in front of him, to change this image to 
the next image.]  
 
 
 
[This image is shown with that slide up animation for the door to get to this image. After that the next 
image is shown with any command from the player by an animation of making the hand and the handle 
to float up to the next image.]  
 
  
23 
 [This image is shown with that animation and there should be some words must be shown ôAgent Zero: 
This vehicle is an Automatic Levitation Vehicleö. After the words appear ance and disappearance, the 
image should go to the next image by a simple full image slide animation.]  
 
 
 
[ This image is shown with that animation and there should be some words must be shown ôAgent Zero: 
This vehicle was following a red line route at a very high speedö. After the words appearance and 
disappearance, the image should go to the next image by a simple full image slide animation.]  
 
 
 
[ This image is shown with that animation and there should be some words must be shown ôAgent Zero: 
Is that a Lab Door or somethingö. After the words appearance and disappearance, the image should go 
to the next image by a simple full image slide animation .] 
 
 
24 
  
[ This image is shown with that animation and there should be some words must be shown ôAgent Zero: 
Is this the Lab of the Scientist I have been looking for?ö. After the words appearance and disappearance, 
the image should go to the next image by a simple full image slide animation.]  
 
Module 3:  
 
 
 
[Directories: If the agent clicks the wall in front of him, it make him move close to the wall like in the next 
image. So give animations in that way and also keep the words mentioned below in a dynamic manner 
at the bottom like the one, I have mentioned f or previous images.]  
ôAgent zero: Mmà I didnÆt find anything here, Is there something behind the wall..? ô    
 
  
 
[ Directories: Like this image ,The previous image(1st image mentioned under module 3 ) would be 
zoomed. And then after that do all the things mentioned under the next image.]  
 
 
 
  
25 
 [Directories: Here in this image, give animations in such a way that the words appear dynamically. And 
then it would take him to the next image.]  
 
 
 
[Directories:  This chess board screen will be opened as soon as the previous image disappears. The 
image that you are going to recreate at this stage will be exactly like the above image. All the positions 
of the pics in the chess board screen  will be exactly like the above image . Here fix the host code as  
ôVWDAZö by default  .And also include the reset button like in the above image . And from this position 
all the pics are accessible , The agent(user) can  
i) Play the game  very well leading to checkmate means it would take him to the next image . 
ii) Or if the user enters the correct host code , it would take him to the next image.  
iii) Or if the user presses the reset button, it will go the initial chess board screen(Partially left 
chess board) as I mentioned earlier , not the starting stage of usual chess board.  
 
 
 
 
In this frame, the agent walks up the corridor and enters the lift room. From there on, he 
uses the lift to move from 28th floor to the base 0th floor.  
[Directory: make sure the frame should move along with the agent, as he approaches the 
lift.]  
 
[Directory: once the agent enters the lift, adjust the frame using animations of similar 
style such that, the agent should turn and look towards the lift entrance and the lift door 
should close, transitioning to image 2.]  
 
26 
  
 
 
Now, the user travels through the lift to the ground floor, from the current (28th) floor.  
[Directory 3: The lift should smoothly move from 28th floor to 0th floor. Slowly change the 
numbers on the display at the top of lift, from 28 to 0, descending one by one. Make sure 
to give each floor, one second in frame, thereby 28 seconds to move from 28th to 0th floor. 
Make the transition between image 2 and image 3 smooth and similar to the given 
prompt.]  
 
 
  
  
 
 
27 
 Module 4:  
 
 
 
[directories : Give animations in such a way that the lift door slowly opens and he encounters a place 
like this in the image above inside the submarine, no objects in this image are accessible except the 
pass lock system ,If the agent or the user touches the pass lock system ,give animations in such a way 
that the pass  lock system is zoomed and then it would  take him to the next image.]  
 
  
 
 [Directories: here in the pass lock system, each key has unique sound when we are pressing it, there 
should a background music starting from the initial stage(introduction(explaining story)) and the music 
should be composed  of four keys sound, the four k eys are 8,1,5,7.When the agent presses the pass 
lock system, then only the background music stops and when the agent types a particular key ,he can 
able to listen to the unique sound of that particular key. For my sake keep the password as 8157. So the 
music should be composed of unique sounds of keys 8,1,5,7.If the agent enters it correctly then the 
vault opens in a dynamic manner and then it would take him to the next image.]  
 
 
 
[directories:  if the user presses the AI machine,it would take him near to the machine and then the next  
image comes up in a dynamic manner]  
28 
  
 
 
[Directories: Here ,Give animations in such a way that he is breaking the glasses using the hammer ,Give 
scattering sound of glasses as the background music(Change background music only in this stage ,For 
all the introduction,module1,2,3,4 keep the same ba ckground music containing the password except 
this part ),After breaking the glasses ,give animations in such a way that he is taking the chip and then 
the next image comes up in a  dynamic  manner.]  
 
 
 
[Directories: Give animations in such a way that the machine gets exploded in a dynamic manner. After 
that it would take him to the next image. Give appropriate background music.]  
 
 
 
[Directories: Give animations in such a way that the president claps his hands and also keep the below 
words in a dynamic manner and also the image and the words should follow a cinematic cutscene style]  
ôJames: Nice man, you faced the impossible, carried the fate of millions in your hands, and returned 
victorious. The world owes you its tomorrow.ö  

